db.questions.insertMany([
{
Science: {
Easy:[
{
Question:	"What does a glaucoma provoke if its not treated?",
Answer: "Blindness",
choiceA: "Deafness",
choiceB: "Tremors",
choiceC: "Nausea",
choiceD: "Blindness"
},
{
Question:	"Which two common household items have a violent chemical reaction when combined?",
Answer: "Sodium bicarbonate and vinegar",
choiceA: "Sodium bicarbonate and Ethanol",
choiceB: "Vinegar and Sodium Hydroxide",
choiceC: "Sodium bicarbonate and vinegar",
choiceD: "Calcium carbonate and Sodium bicarbonate"
},
{
Question:	"Au is an abbreviation for which chemical element?",
Answer: "Gold",
choiceA: "Gold",
choiceB: "Silver",
choiceC: "Copper",
choiceD: "Iron"
},
{
Question:	"How is tooth cavity usually fixed?",
Answer: "By filling it",
choiceA: "By extracting it",
choiceB: "By cleaning it",
choiceC: "By replacing it with dentures",
choiceD: "By filling it"
},
{
Question:	"Which is the name of the most extended artery of the human body?",
Answer: "Aorta",
choiceA: "Aorta",
choiceB: "Axilla",
choiceC: "Arteria Dorsalis",
choiceD: "Thoracic"
}
],
Medium: [{
Question:	"When are young elephants considered to be adults?",
Answer: "12 to 15 years old",
choiceA: "12 to 15 years old",
choiceB: "13 to 16 years old",
choiceC: "11 to 14 years old",
choiceD: "10 to 13 years old"
},
{
Question:	"Which part of the eye responds to light?",
Answer: "Retina",
choiceA: "Sclera",
choiceB: "Cornea",
choiceC: "Retina",
choiceD: "Iris"
},
{
Question:	"What's the colostrum?",
Answer: "The first breast milk",
choiceA: "The first period",
choiceB: "The first breast milk",
choiceC: "The first pregnancy",
choiceD: "The first..."
},
{
Question:	"What is plastic made of?",
Answer: "Oil",
choiceA: "Leaves",
choiceB: "Oil",
choiceC: "Rocks",
choiceD: "Wood"
},
{
Question:	"What does vexillology study?",
Answer: "",
choiceA: "Study of Glands",
choiceB: "Study of Worms",
choiceC: "Study of Tides",
choiceD: "Study of Flags"
}
],
Hard: [{
Question:	"What's the name of the chronic mood disorder that alternates periods of hypomanic symptoms with periods of mild depression?",
Answer: "Cyclothymia",
choiceA: "Bipolar disorder",
choiceB: "Major Depression",
choiceC: "Cyclothymia",
choiceD: "Dysthymia"
},
{
Question:	"What prevents virus replication?",
Answer: "Interferons",
choiceA: "Algesia",
choiceB: "Anodonta",
choiceC: "Dorsalon",
choiceD: "Interferons"
},
{
Question:	"What does a speleologist study?",
Answer: "Caves",
choiceA: "Sun",
choiceB: "Caves",
choiceC: "Flags",
choiceD: "Waves"
},
{
Question:	"What is aboulia?",
Answer: "A decrease of motivation",
choiceA: "A decrease of emotion",
choiceB: "A decrease of motivation",
choiceC: "A sudden decrease of happiness",
choiceD: "A decrease of energy"
},
{
Question:	"The Statue of Liberty is covered in what material?",
Answer: "Copper",
choiceA: "Lead",
choiceB: "Cadium",
choiceD: "Scandium"
choiceC: "Copper",
}
]
}
}
]);
